Like the sun burnin’ in the daytime
낮에 타는 태양
새벽의 별 같아
Like a star at dawn
You catch up in my mind
내 세상 속엔 네가
Every single day
매일 떠오르니까
Baby don’t cry
Baby don’t cry 꽉 잡아 여길 떠나
Hold me tight
Let’s leave together
To a place where we’ll stick forever
너와 내가 영원할 곳으로
Cuz I can’t stop
Cuz I can’t stop 도망가자 여긴 폭탄
Let’s get out of here
Through a grenade
It’s all blue things that destroying us
우릴 파괴하는 것들뿐이야
You are magic in my mind
Although they said there’s no fate
정해진 운명은 없다고 하지만
Keep thinkin’ tens of thousands of times
수만 번 생각해 봐도
Since I was born
눈을 뜨고 태어났을 때부터 난
Born to born to born to love ya
Yeah yeah
Oh
Born to born to born to love ya
Hypnotized in-
홀린 듯이 뒤꽁무니 쫓아가지
Goin’ after you
Hypnotized in-
홀린 듯이 더 빠져 Deep Follow your lips
Fallin’ deeply to deep side
Follow your lips
네 맘에 문 열어 Door
To ya heart, gonna open the door, door
파고들어 너의 Core
Snuggle into your core
Forever ever all long 갈 수 있게
Forever ever all long
The way we can go
Abracadabra
Born to love ya I want you all
Born to love ya 널 원해 전부 다
거절은 거절해 난
I refuse to your refusal
Ain’t gonna keep-in anything but u
너 말고 아무것도 안 담아
네 품에 난 갇혀
Trapped in your arms
감싸줘 Xs and Os
Wrap me up Xs and Os
In err single life
널 반복되는 매 생마다
Born to love ya, Gotcha
Born to love ya 찾았어
Again & again 돌고 돌아서
Again & again all around
Period (point)
마침표 팍
You’re my last thing
넌 내 마지막
영원히 놓지 않아
Will never let you go
No doubt
Wide open eyes
눈이 번쩍 뜨여졌어 너란 보석
You’re my treasure
너를 갖고 싶어 훔쳤으니까
Stole it cuz I want you
나를 던져 너를 건져
Throw me out bring you out
Come closer
우리 사랑의 시작일 뿐이야
It’s just the beginning of our love
You are magic in my mind
정해진 운명은 없다고 하지만
Although they said there’s no fate
Keep thinkin’ tens of thousands of times
수만 번 생각해 봐도
눈을 뜨고 태어났을 때부터 난
Since I was born
Born to born to born to love ya
Yeah yeah
Oh
Born to born to born to love ya
‘Til the sunrise
아침 해가 뜰 때까지
Let’s speed it up let’s speed it up
Run away to the end of the earth
달아나 지구 끝까지
Let’s speed it up let’s speed it up
Let’s go to an island just the two of us
둘만의 섬으로 가자
No one else, Baby you’re all that I need
다른 사람은 안 돼 Baby you’re all that I need
No
넌 내 삶의 Climax
You’re the Climax of my life
뜨거워져 Burning in love
Burnin’ and Burning in love
Burn it up, You’re my adrenaline
하얗게 불태워 You’re my adrenaline
넌 내 삶의 Climax
You’re the Climax of my life
Burnin’ and Burning in love
뜨거워져 Burning in love
Burn it up, You’re my adrenaline
하얗게 불태워 You’re my adrenaline
Born to born to born to
Oh oh oh oh oh
Love ya love ya love ya
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Born to born to born to
Oh oh oh oh oh
Love ya love ya love ya
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Born to born to born to love ya